(Sheldon:)Hmm.
What could we do that's fun?
What could we do that's different?
What could we do that's free?
Got it! We order a pizza.
(Penny:)Are you kidding? That's what you
always do. Think harder.
(Sheldon:)You're right. You're right.
Got it!
(Sheldon:)We order calzones, cut them open,
eat them like pizza.
All right! All right!
I'll shake the brain bush one more time,
(Sheldon:)see what falls out.
Got it! There's a live-action
role-playing group
(Sheldon:)that meets every Thursday night
in Griffith Park
(Sheldon:)and reenacts battles
from Lord of the Rings.
Okay, tell me more
about this calzone idea.
(Leonard:)You know what?
Why don't we just ease into this.
(Leonard:)Let's go for a walk
and see if we find a new restaurant.
(Sheldon:)Any chance that restaurant
is near Griffith Park?